《旺达幻视》前情提要
Previously on WandaVision...
你根本没有费心隐藏你的超能力
You made no effort to conceal your abilities.
-我不想再躲躲藏藏了  小幻  -你有什么瞒着我的
- Well, I'm tired of hiding, Vis. - What aren't you telling me?
你得阻止她
You have to stop her.
让她停下
Just make her stop!
你不能像控制别人那样控制我
You can't control me the way you do them.
是吗
Can't I?
但是她在让这世界上唯一的合成人
She has the world's only vibranium synthezoid
跟她演《郊区版老爸最知道》
playing Father-Knows-Best-In-Suburbia.
等他知道真相后会怎么样
What happens when he learns the truth?
你劫持了整个镇的人
You've taken an entire town hostage.
拿着枪的人可不是我  局长
Well, I'm not the one with the guns, Director.
我曾经也有一个哥哥
I had a brother.
他叫皮特
His name was Pietro.
他是被奥创杀死的
He was killed by Ultron.
一位消失很久的哥哥
Long lost bro get to
来给他的臭妹妹一个紧紧的拥抱了
squeeze his stinkin' sister to death or what?
她给皮特重新选角了
She recast Pietro?
漫威
影业
♪ 旺达  旺达幻视 ♪
♪ Wanda Wanda Vision ♪
♪ 别企图对抗混乱  别质疑你做了什么 ♪
♪ Don't try to fight the chaos Don't question what you've done ♪
旺达·马克西莫夫
♪ 游戏可以玩我们 ♪
♪ The game can try to play us ♪
♪ 别让欢乐停下 ♪
♪ Don't let it stop the fun ♪
♪ 有些日子非常混沌 ♪
♪ Some days it's all confusion ♪
♪ 来得快  去得快  但如果一切皆爲虚幻 ♪
♪ Easy come and easy go But if it's all illusion ♪
幻视
♪ 坐好  享受节目 ♪
♪ Sit back, enjoy the show ♪
♪ 我们继续下去吧 ♪
♪ Let's keep it going ♪
♪ 度过每个扭曲的一天 ♪
♪ Through each distorted day ♪
{\an8\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\fs34\pos(190.6,141.2)\c&HE9E1EF&\1a&H00&\3c&HFF55AA&\3a&H00&\bord0\shad1\4c&HFF55AA&\4a&H00&}\h\h\h艾格妮丝
比利·马克西莫夫  汤米·马克西莫夫
♪ 我们继续下去吧 ♪
♪ Let's keep it going ♪
♪ 尽管无从知道 ♪
♪ Though there may be no way of knowing ♪
皮特·马克西莫夫
饰演自己
♪ 谁会路过一起玩 ♪
♪ Who's coming by to play ♪
{\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\fs54\frz28\fad(0,0)\bord0\shad0\blur0\pos(166.6,251.9)\c&H81CFFF&\1a&H00&}旺达幻视
{\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\fs44\frz28\fad(0,0)\bord0\shad0\blur0\c&H1ED8B1&\1a&H00&\pos(254.7,53)}第一季
{\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\fs40\frz28\fad(0,0)\bord0\shad0\blur0\c&HE300FF&\1a&H00&\pos(343.5,206.9)}第
六
集
万圣节是个神奇的节日
Halloween's a magical holiday.
它的重点是家庭  朋友
All about family, friends,
和可以扮成其他人一天的兴奋感
and the thrill of getting to be someone else for a day.
错了  万圣节的重点是糖果
Wrong! Halloween's about candy.
还有吓唬人  但糖果更重要
And scaring people, but mostly candy.
你的服装呢  汤米
Where's your costume, Tommy?
这就是我的服装  我是双胞胎里酷的那个
This is my costume. I'm the cool twin.
那我是什么
What does that make me?
呆呆龙
A dorksaurus rex.
没有那种恐龙
Not a real dinosaur.
天啊
Man.
他打鼾都那么酷
He even snores cool.
-我要吵醒他  -别
- I'm gonna go wake him up. - Don't!
你怕了吗
You scared?
他是我们的舅舅  我怎么会怕
He's our uncle. Why would I be scared?
因爲现在是下午四点
'Cause it's four o'clock in the afternoon.
你偷偷担心他是个吸血鬼
You're secretly afraid he's a vampire.
-我没有  -你就有
- No, I'm not. - Yes, you are.
我没有
No, I'm not.
血浓于水  我给你们看吧
Blood is thicker than water! I show you!
最好是有人流血  摔坏或者着火了
Somebody better be bleeding, broken, or on fire.
妈妈  你是老红帽吗
Mom. Are you old Red Riding Hood?
我是一名索科威亚算命师
I'm a Sokovian fortune teller.
那真是太...
That is so...
-酷了  -蠢了
- Rad. - ...lame.
是"蠢"
"Lame."
比我们得伤寒那年妈妈给我们做的服装还难看
Worse than the costumes mom made us the year we got typhus.
不给糖就捣蛋!
要分享哦.
我印象里可不是那样
That's not exactly how I remember it.
你可能压抑了很多创伤
You probably suppressed a lot of the trauma.
皮特舅舅来后  妈妈就一直怪怪的
Mom has been weird since Uncle Pietro got here.
我觉得是因爲她好久没见他了
I think it's because she hasn't seen him in a long time.
而且他就是所谓的"大男孩"
And he's what you call, "A man child."
好服装啊  妹夫
Sweet costume bro-ham-in-law.
我猜猜  交通灯
Let me guess. Uh, traffic light.
剥了一半的玉米
Half-shucked corn.
鼻屎
A booger!
-对了  -棒
- Yes. - Yes!
谢谢你迁就我
Well, thank you for humoring me
穿得这么滑稽  亲爱的
and wearing this ridiculous get-up, honey.
我的衣橱里没有其他衣服了  所以
Well, there were no other clothes in my closet, so...
你真不可救药  亲爱的
You are incorrigible, darling.
我知道你偷偷喜欢墨西哥摔跤手
I know you have a secret thing for Mexican wrestlers.
我好喜欢
Mi gusta mucho.
墨西哥辣肉酱
Chili con carne.
怎么样  孩子们
What do you say, boys?
谁准备好吃第一口高果糖玉米糖浆了
Who's ready for that first hit of high fructose corn syrup?
-锁头了  -快走开
- Yes! Headlock! - Get out of here, get out of here.
你没怎么跟我讲过你哥哥
Never told me much about your brother.
没想到他这么...
I had no idea he'd be so...
开始
Go!
擅长带孩子
Great with kids.
是啊  他真是充满惊喜
Yeah. He's just full of surprises.
那你今晚开心了  亲爱的
Well, you have fun tonight, darling.
什么  什么意思  你不都穿好要走了吗
What? What do you mean? You're all dressed and ready to go.
我在卧底
I'm undercover.
万圣节是爱惹事的青少年的狂欢盛典
Halloween is a bacchanal for adolescent trouble-makers
社区联防是唯一能阻止树木
and the neighborhood watch is the only thing that stands
挂上厕纸的人了
between the trees and the toilet paper.
-不  你不该...  -什么
- No, that's not what you're supposed to-- - What?
好吧
Well...
你可没说你有安排了
You didn't tell me you had plans.
我现在说了
Well, I am telling you now.
妈妈和爸爸近来  也不是吵架  就不一样了
Mom and Dad have been, not fighting, just, like, different.
这是他们的第一个万圣节  你必须在场
It's their first Halloween. You have to be there.
有什么大问题
What's the big dealio?
兄弟另外有事  双胞胎今晚又需要个父亲人物
Big guy has a conflict, twins need a father figure for the night.
没事的  妹妹  我也有XY染色体
Don't sweat it, sis. I got the old XY chromosome.
皮舅舅来救场
Uncle P to the rescue, huh?
这就行了  问题解决了
There you go. Problem solved.
今晚吓得开心  孩子们
You have a spooky time tonight, kids.
-晚安  爸爸  -再见  爸爸
- Goodnight, Dad! - Bye, Dad.
旺达
Wanda?
乖乖的
Be good.
我闻到了犯罪
I smell crime.
别那样
Don't do that!
你把水气球都放哪了
Where do you keep your water balloons?
什么  我们没有水气球
What? We don't have water balloons.
那这些剃须膏要往哪里放
Where are we gonna put all this shaving cream?
-是比利的主意  -我是汤米
- It was Billy's idea. - I'm Tommy.
你可别忘了
And don't you forget it!
你连服装都没有
You don't even have a costume.
好吧  但...记住  我们可是受尊敬的一家
Okay, but... Just remember that this is a respectable family.
如果我看到你们搞怪
If I see any funny business,
我就用魔法把你们变成腌鲱鱼
I am going to magic you into a pickled herring.
一小时内完成完全分析
I wanna see a full work-up inside the hour.
-是  长官  -海沃德
- Yes, sir. - Hayward.
海沃德
Hayward!
你派导弹进去  是断了我们的后路
You cut us off at the knees, sending in that missile.
我们现在清楚在跟什么样的人打交道了
Now we know who we're dealing with.
他来了
Hey, there he is.
差点被自己的杀人小队杀掉的人
The guy who almost got murdered by his own murder squad.
你爲我工作吗
You work for me?
-我还真不知道  -她是我的人
- I actually don't know. - She's with me.
这样啊  你们哪个是嘴上不饶人的闺蜜
I see. And which one of you is the sassy best friend?
你没功夫贬低同事了
There is no time for you to diminish your colleagues
你就要掀起一场你赢不了的战争了
when you're about to start a war you can't win.
马克西莫夫本就不可能跟我们谈判
Maximoff was never gonna negotiate with us.
我们干掉她  这整个噩梦才会结束
We take her out, this whole nightmare ends.
这不好说
We don't know that.
我们根本不知道
We actually have no idea
如果旺达死了  那里和这里都会发生什么
what will happen in there or out here if Wanda dies.
怎么  我们就对它投降吗
So, what? We just surrender to that?
绝不可能
Not happening.
我们打不过她
We can't outgun her.
显然  跟她对立只让事情更糟了
And clearly antagonizing her is only making things worse.
如果旺达是问题所在  那解铃还须系铃人
If Wanda is the problem, she has to be our solution.
兰博上尉  你已经成了此次任务的阻碍
Captain Rambeau, you have become an impediment to this mission.
总是替超能力人士说话
Constantly advocating on behalf of super-powered individuals.
是啊  我清楚你跟卡罗尔·丹弗斯的渊源
Yes, I know your history with Carol Danvers.
你们那些离开的人
You know, you people who left,
仍可以奢侈地保持乐观
still have the luxury of optimism.
你根本无法想象我们的情况
You have no idea what it was like.
爲了持续下去都需要付出什么
What it took to keep the lights on.
别拿过去五年作爲懦弱的藉口
Don't use the last five years as an excuse to be a coward.
或许你母亲死时你没在也是好事
Maybe it's a good thing you weren't here when your mother died.
因爲你显然没有做这份工作的勇气
Because clearly you don't have the stomach for this job.
带她离开我的基地  马上  把他们都带走
Get her off my base. Now. All of 'em.
好了  走吧
All right. Come on. Let's go.
海沃德的行事已经远超了他的临时权力
Hayward is way overstepping his provisional authority.
他就想找个理由排挤走我们
He was looking for a reason to sideline us.
他有什么计划
He's up to something.
走  都进去
Let's go. Everybody in!
怎么没人把计划告诉我
Why didn't anyone tell me the plan?
-你没事吧  -嗯  走吧
- You okay? - Yeah. Let's move.
天剑局
好了  游戏时间到
This is it. Game time.
这又不是比赛  汤米
It's not a competition, Tommy.
-你赢了不就是了  -汤米
- It is if you're a winner. - Tommy.
掀起地狱腥风吧  恶魔之子
Unleash hell, demon spawn.
你记得爸妈死后我们在
Do you remember when we were at the orphanage
孤儿院时吗
after mom and dad died?
那个总想
What was the name of that
偷你靴子的小孩叫什么来着
kid who was always trying to steal your boots?
就是那个...皮肤有问题的
You know, he was the one... He had the... He had the skin thing.
你在考我
You're testing me.
我没有
No, I'm not.
没事  我知道我变样了
Hey, it's cool. I know I look different.
你爲什么...变样了
Why do you... look different?
你说呢  如果我找到了仙境
You tell me. I mean, if I found Shangri-La,
我也不会想被提醒过去的样子
I wouldn't wanna be reminded of the past either.
下一家  妈妈
Next house, Mom.
这是个小企业家啊
Junior entrepreneur, over here.
让你的皮舅舅
How about you let Uncle P
帮你最大化糖果收购吧
help you maximize your candy acquisition, huh?
好啊  海扁
Yeah. Kick-ass!
"我觉得需要..."
"I feel the need..."
"速度"
"For speed."
海扁
Kick-ass.
好啊  赫
Oh, hey, Herb.
巡逻得如何了
How's patrol going?
目前很平静  等一下
Eh, quiet, so far. Hold up, will you?
再说一遍
Say again.
所有糖果都消失了吗
All the candy has disappeared?
什么  谁把我的糖抢走了
What? Who took my candy?
现在所有南瓜灯都被砸了
And now all the jack-o'-lanterns have been smashed.
现在大家身上全都是傻兮兮的飘带吗
And now everyone's covered in silly string?
抱歉  旺达  我要走了
Sorry, Wanda, I gotta bounce.
也许幻视可以帮你
Well, maybe Vision can help you out.
幻视  他今天不值班
Vision? Oh, he's not on duty.
我...我以爲他...
Oh! I... I thought he...
你需要我做什么吗  旺达
Is there something I can do for you, Wanda?
你想改变些什么吗
Do you want something changed?
不  没事  没关系
No. It's fine. Never mind.
好吧  安了
All right. Peace.
你好啊
Hey! How's it going?
万圣节快乐
Happy Halloween.
我好饿  我什么都会吃
I'm so hungry, I'd eat anything.
饿了吗  我记得饥饿的感觉
Hungry? I remember hungry.
我以前经常很饿
I used to be like that all the time.
然后你做了什么
What did you do?
来点魔法酸奶  哥们儿
Snacked on Yo-Magic, bro.
{\an8\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\frz8\fs22\b1\pos(56,20.2)\4c&H0255EF&\4a&H00&\bord2\3c&H0154F0&\3a&H00&\shad2\c&HB8DBF3&\1a&H00&}全新
{\an8\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\frz0\fs34\b1\bord2\shad2\c&HB8DBF3&\1a&H00&\3c&HAB7A10&\3a&H00&\4c&HBA870B&\4a&H00&\pos(127.2,29.6)}魔法酸奶
{\an8\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\frz8\fs20\b1\pos(66,150)\c&HA2A1C1&\1a&H00&\3c&HB87E2E&\3a&H00&\shad0\bord3}草莓味
我现在都有时间翅翅玩玩了
Now I have time to hang fin.
能给我来点吗
Can I have some?
给  小家伙
Here you go, little dude.
魔法酸奶
魔法酸奶  生存者专用零食
Yo-Magic! The snack for survivors!
{\an8\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\frz18\fs38\b1\pos(56,20.2)\4c&H0255EF&\4a&H00&\bord2\3c&H0154F0&\3a&H00&\shad2\c&HF7F5F7&\1a&H00&}全新
{\an8\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\frz0\fs44\b1\bord2\shad2\3c&HAB7A10&\3a&H00&\4c&HBA870B&\4a&H00&\pos(192.7,5.2)\c&HF4F1F4&\1a&H00&}魔法酸奶
{\an8\fn字魂52号-阿开漫画体\frz8\fs30\b1\3c&HB87E2E&\3a&H00&\shad0\bord3\c&HF5CFEF&\1a&H00&\pos(87.7,204)}草莓味
皇冠影院
超人特工队
天生一对
太扫兴了
This is so lame.
真不敢相信你逼他们把糖都还回去了
I can't believe you're making them return all the candy.
真不敢相信你竟然做了这么坏的榜样
I can't believe what a bad influence you are.
你吃错什么药了
Who beefed in your borscht?
我只是想做我该做的事
I'm just trying to do my part, okay?
突然出现在镇上
Come to town unexpectedly,
和我的妹夫产生矛盾
create tension with the brother-in-law,
跟孩子们一起惹麻烦  最后惹你难过
stir up trouble with the rugrats, and ultimately give you grief.
这不就是你想要的吗
I mean, that's what you wanted, isn't it?
你的口音怎么回事
What happened to your accent?
你的又是怎么回事
What happened to yours?
细节太模糊了
Details are fuzzy, man.
我在街上莫名其妙被人打了一枪
I got shot like a chump on the street for no reason at all
然后我好像就听到了你的召唤
and the next thing I know, I heard you calling me.
我知道你需要我
I knew you needed me.
皮舅舅  你猜怎么着
Uncle P, guess what?
几个街区外在发大块糖果  妈妈  我们能去吗
They've got full-size candy bars a few blocks up. Mom, can we go?
下一站  蛀牙小镇
Next stop, Cavity Town.
好嘞  小家伙
Right on, little dude.
有老舅必有小外甥
Chip off the old Maximoff block.
你有超高速能力
You've got super speed!
-真的吗  -是的
- I do? - Yeah!
没事的  宝贝
It's okay, baby.
你可以慢点  你也可以...
You can take it slow, and you can--
如果你要突破音速屏障
If you're gonna break the sound barrier,
请带上你的兄弟一起
please just take your brother with you.
-真的吗  -真的吗
- Really? - Really?
真的  以及拜托你们记住
Really. Yeah. And please just remember to--
不要越过艾利斯大道
Don't go past Ellis Avenue.
我们知道  妈妈  我们知道
We know, Mom. We know.
小心点
Hey! Be careful.
我只是想做我该做的事
I'm just trying to do my part, okay?
突然出现在镇上
Come to town unexpectedly,
和我的妹夫产生矛盾
create tension with the brother-in-law...
那是谁啊
Who is that?
旺达的哥哥来到了镇上
Wanda's brother came to town.
他的脸不对
He brought the wrong face.
这边
Over here.
-你的口音怎么回事  -你的又是怎么回事
- What happened to your accent? - What happened to yours?
我们不该在这里待太久
We shouldn't hang out here too long.
给我两秒钟
Uh, give me two seconds.
我需要黑进基地的安全网络
I just need to hack into the secure network on the base.
搞定
Donezo.
好了  应该可以接触到
Now, should be able to access the data
海沃德装置上的数据了
on Hayward's devices.
有点意思
Oh. That's interesting.
伙计们  海沃德有办法看到边界内
Guys, Hayward figured out a way to look through the boundary.
但是他却没有告诉组里的人
And he didn't share it with the group.
这是旺达吗
Is this Wanda, right here?
不  这个项目在追踪振金的衰变特征
No. The program is tracking the decay signature of vibranium.
是幻视  等等
Vision. Wait.
海沃德爲什么要追踪幻视
Why is Hayward tracking Vision?
我不知道  我目前只有这个权限
I don't know. This is all I can access so far.
那这些点是西景居民吗
These other dots, those are Westview residents?
紧挨着幻视的那些是的
The ones in Vision's immediate vicinity, yeah.
那海沃德现在肯定知道准确人数了
So Hayward must have an accurate headcount by now.
也差不多了解他们的状况了
And some sense of their well-being.
这些在镇边缘的人
These people, near the edge of town...
他们几乎一动不动
They're barely moving.
他们还活着吗
Are they alive?
人物重连中
打扰一下
Say, excuse me.
女士
Ma'am?
他们是你家孩子吗
Are those your children?
你在等什么吗
Are you waiting for something?
万圣节快乐
Happy Halloween!
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick-or-treat?
艾格妮丝
Agnes?
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
镇广场吓人大会在哪
Town Square Scare. Where is it?
在镇广场吧  应该是
Oh, well, the Town Square. I expect.
转错弯了
Took a wrong turn.
迷路了
Got lost.
可你不就是在这个镇上长大的吗
In the town you grew up in?
没事的
It's all right.
你...
You...
你是复仇者
You're one of the Avengers.
你是幻视
You're Vision.
你是来救我们的吗
Are you here to help us?
我确实是幻视  我确实想帮忙
I am Vision. I do want to help.
但复仇者是什么
But what's an Avenger?
什么
What?
你怎么会不知道
Why don't you know?
我死了吗
Am I dead?
没有  你怎么会那么想
No, no. Why would you think that?
因爲你死了
Because you are.
因爲我什么
'Cause I'm what?
死了
Dead.
Dead!
死了
艾格尼丝  我想联系西景镇外面
Agnes, it is my intention to reach those outside of Westview
弄清我们现在的状况
and make sense of our situation.
怎么做
How?
谁都不能离开
No one leaves.
旺达都不许我们想这事
Wanda won't even let us think about it.
全完了
All is lost.
艾格尼丝
Agnes...
艾格尼丝  冷静一下
Agnes, please calm down.
艾格尼丝  求你别这样...
Agnes! Please...
我会解决的  艾格尼丝  我保证
I will fix this, Agnes. I promise.
好啊  邻居
Okey-dokey, neighbor.
万圣节愉快哟
Happy Halloweenie!
艾利斯大道
医疗记录
莫妮卡·兰博
来了
That's it.
我回到六边域的办法一小时就到
My way back into the Hex will be here in an hour.
得去山那边跟我的朋友碰头
Just gotta meet my guy over the ridge.
行动吧
Let's roll.
你们不能那样做
You can't do that.
当然能  我是短路点火的专家
Sure we can. I'm a whiz at hot-wiring cars.
你们不能回到六边域里
You can't go back into the Hex.
最糟糕的情况是
Worst case scenario,
旺达除掉我的自由意志  让我穿上超低腰牛仔裤
Wanda removes my free will and puts me in ultra-low-rise jeans.
海沃德给你做了血液检查
Hayward has your blood work.
你已经进入边界两次了  莫妮卡
You've gone through the boundary twice already, Monica.
里面的能量在分子层面上
The energy inside has re-written your cells
两次改写了你的细胞
on a molecular level twice.
它在改变你
It's changing you.
我看过够一辈子量的化验报告了
Seen enough lab results to last me a lifetime.
细胞转移  细胞缓解
Cells metastasizing, cells in remission.
我知道旺达的感受  不帮到她我不罢休
I know what Wanda's feeling and I won't stop until I help her.
好吧
Okay.
好
但我要留在这
But I'm staying here.
你不能留在这
You can't stay here.
-这里不安全  -达西  你说什么
- It's not safe. - What? Darcy, what are you talkin' about?
我还没突破海沃德的最后一道防火墙
I haven't made it through Hayward's last firewall.
里面肯定有重要的东西
There's something big here.
能帮到我们的东西  我能肯定
Something that can help us. I know it.
好吧
Fine. Fine.
我发给你地点
I'll drop you the location,
你尽快到那里跟我们会合
you meet us out there as soon as you can.
老天爷啊
Holy shmacaroni.
是不是很热闹
Isn't it great?
新泽西州西景镇真是魅力天堂
Damn it, if Westview, New Jersey isn't charming as hell.
我知道你肯定觉得我变成足球妈妈了
Now, I know that you think that I've have gone full soccer mom.
特指花许多时间带孩子
参加各种活动的妈妈
-没错  -但是这真的很棒  对吗
- Yeah. - But it really is nice, right?
对
Yeah.
我觉得爸爸妈妈肯定会喜欢的
I think Mom and Dad would've loved it.
是的  我觉得也是
Yeah. I think they would have.
你之前都把这些孩子藏在哪儿了
Where were you hiding these kids up till now?
-什么  -我猜
- What? - I assume
他们都一直乖乖地在牀上睡觉呢
they were sleeping peacefully in their beds.
除了偶尔在节日里跑跑龙套
No need to traumatize beyond
没必要给他们造成更多创伤了  是不是
the occasional holiday episode cameo, right?
-不  -你一直都是双胞胎中更有同理心的那个
- No... - You were always the empathetic twin.
-不  我没  -别误会我
- I don't... I didn't... - Don't get me wrong.
你对这个情况的伦理问题
You've handled the ethical considerations
处理得尽量好了
of this scenario as best you could.
家人和夫妻都待在一起
Families and couples stay together,
大部分人的性格都和本质相差不大
most personalities aren't far off from what's underneath,
人们的工作都更好
people got better jobs,
毫无疑问  发型也更棒
better haircuts, for sure.
你不觉得这是错的
You don't think it's wrong?
什么  你在开玩笑吗
What, are you kidding?
说真的  我感觉很震撼
I'm impressed! Seriously.
从给人们带来噩梦和从手里发射红色法术
It's a big leap from giving people nightmares
到变成这样  可是一个很大的飞跃呢
and shooting red wiggly-woos out of your hands.
你到底是怎么做到这些的
How'd you even do all this?
我不是什么陌生人
Hey, I'm not some stranger
我也不是你的丈夫
and I'm not your husband.
你可以和我聊聊
You can talk to me.
我不知道我是怎么做到的
I don't know how I did it.
我
I...
我只记得我感觉非常孤独
I only remember feeling completely alone.
非常空虚  我只是
Empty. I just...
永无止境的虚无
Endless nothingness.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
视障
秘密武器
绝密
海沃德·T
海沃德  你这个卑鄙的混蛋
Hayward, you sneaky bastard.
收件人  詹姆斯·吴  联调局
开始行动
Move out.
是幻视  他在干什么
Vision. What's he doing?
振金
他是真的想出来  是不是
He really does want out, doesn't he?
不好
Oh, no.
你们爲什么不帮帮他
Why aren't you helping him?
停下  他开始碎裂了
Stop! He's coming apart!
他是真的想出来  是不是
He really does want out doesn't he?
比利
Whoa, Billy!
你怎么了
Are you okay?
妈妈
Mom!
妈妈  妈妈  妈妈
Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom!
什么  怎么了  比利
What? What is it, Billy?
我脑海里听见了爸爸的声音  他出事了
I hear Dad in my head. He's in trouble.
放开我  你干什么
Let me go! What are you doing?
帮帮他  放开我
Help him! Let me go!
帮帮我
Help!
帮帮里面的人
The people need help.
我不明白  我这是怎么了
I don't understand. What's happening to me?
他在哪儿  你爸爸在哪儿
Where is he? Where's your dad?
别着急  老妹
Hey, don't sweat it, sis.
你那死人丈夫又不会死第二回
It's not like your dead husband can die twice.
比利  我需要你集中精神
Billy, I need you to focus.
我说不好  我看到了一些
I can't tell. I see these...
士兵
...soldiers.
他们觉得爸爸快死了
They think he's dying.
吉米  吉米  你看见了吗  出事了
Jimmy. Jimmy, do you see that? Something's happening!
它正在移动  走  快走
It's moving! Go, go!
走  快走  快点
Go, go, go! Move, move, move!
你是认真的吗
Are you serious right now?
停下
Hey! Stop!
该死
Oh, fudge.
油炸煎饼
加速  开快点
Push it! Faster!
西景镇
欢迎来到西景镇
罗迪欧汽车销售
二手车
呼叫  有人能听到吗
Come in. Anyone read me?
有人听得见吗
Anyone hear my voice?
有人能听到我吗
Does anyone read me?
有人能收到吗  完毕
Anyone read me? Over.
请稍后